Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Residential projects., 1939-1970
  - Subseries C: Additions and renovations., 1939-1968.; 30 map folders
    - ., 1939-1945 (Folder 184)
      - Yarbrough Caretaker's Cottage., 1945.; 3.; 1 item.
        Yarbrough Caretaker's Cottage
        1224 Tremaine, Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, section, elevations.
        Owner: Dr's John D. & ElsieTremaine.
    - ., 1946 (Folder 185)
      - Smallberg residence., 1946?; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 461. Addition to Smallberg residence
        1578 North Doheny Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. H.E. Smallberg.
      - Levinson residence., 1946.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 510. Addition to Levinson residence
        8015 McGroaty, Sunland, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. Levinson.
      - Whittaker residence., 1946.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 517. Remodeling of Whittaker residence
        15963 Valley Vista Blvd. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. C.K. Whitteker.
      - Dunn Garage House., 1946.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 523. Dunn Garage House
        4739 Beck Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, section, elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. J. Dunn.
      - Silverman rooming house., 1946.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 550. Silverman rooming house relocation and remodeling
        446 Centennial St. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. Juba Silverman.
    - (1 of 2)., 1947 (Folder 186)
      - Nelson residence., 1947.; 1.; 2 items.
        Addition to Nelson residence
        11114 Valley Spring Lane, North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Fred Nelson.
      - Pedretti residence., 1947?; 2.; 1 item.
        Addition to Pedretti residence
        Cohasset St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. A.W. Pedretti.
      - Russell residence., 1947.; 3.; 1 item.
        Addition to Russell residence
        6456 Hazeltine Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. O. Russell.
      - Leon residence., 1947.; 4.; 2 items.
        Addition to Leon residence
        4420 Sunset Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Al Leon.
      - Ostadal garage., 1947.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 602. Ostadal garage remodel & addition
        19057 Arminta St. Reseda, CA.
        Owner: John Ostadal.
      - Dozier residence., 1947.; 6.; 2 items.
        Job Number 605. Addition to Dozier residence
        11470 Eldridge St. San Fernando, CA.
        Owner: Elizabeth Gist Dozier, M.D.
      - Caruso garage., 1947.; 7.; 1 item.
        Job Number 606. Caruso garage
        West Ridge Rd. San Fernando, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Anthony Caruso.
      - Biroc residence., 1947.; 8.; 3 items.
        Job Number 615. Addition to Biroc residence
        5220 Topeka Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, interior and exterior elevations and sections.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Biroc.
    - (2 of 2)., 1947 (Folder 187)
      - Blaine residence., 1947.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 621. Addition to Blaine residence
        10945 Bluffside, North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. Blaine.
      - Meagher residence., 1947.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 624. Addition to Meagher residence
        4023 Woodman Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Chas. S. Meagher.
      - Van Enger residence., 1947.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 627. Addition to Van Enger residence
        5743 Hazeltine Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Chas. J. Van Enger.
      - Barron residence., 1947.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 645. Addition to Barron residence
        4106 Alcove Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Charles H. Barron.
      - Moores residence., 1947.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 646. Addition to Moores residence
        4554 Cartwright. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Richard Moores.
      - Filippini residence., 1947.; 6.; 1 item.
        Job Number 646. Addition to Filippini residence
        6941 Coldwater Canyon Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. J. Filippini.
      - Rolin residence., 1947.; 7.; 2 items.
        Job Number 656. Addition to Rolin residence
        11700 Laurelwood Dr. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. J. Rolin.
    - ., 1948 (Folder 188)
      - Murphy residence., 1948.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 527B. Second story addition to Murphy residence
      - Jacobs residence., 1948.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 668. Jacobs residence remodeling
        12903 Dickens St. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H.R. Jacobs.
      - Leeper bath house., 1948.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 672. Leeper bath house
        11915 Kling St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W.S. Leeper.
      - Ravetta residence., 1948.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 692. Addition to Ravetta residence
        4712 Louise St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Lucian Ravetta.
      - Kipp residence., 1948.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 700. Addition to Kipp residence
        4935 Morse Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harold W. Kipp.
      - Keating residence., 1948.; 6.; 1 item.
        Job Number 701. Addition to Keating residence
        Mound View Ave. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Keating.
      - Dodds residence., 1948.; 7.; 2 items.
        Job Number 706. Addition to Dodds residence
        5339 Newcastle Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Torrence Dodds.
      - Busch garage., 1948.; 8.; 1 item.
        Job Number 740. Busch garage
        4601 Balboa Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, interior and exterior elevations, section and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Niven Busch.
    - ., 1949 (Folder 189)
      - Loughan garage., 1949.; 1.; 2 items.
        Loughan garage
        4221 Vanetta Dr. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Thomas Loughan.
      - McMahon residence., 1949.; 2.; 1 item.
        Addition & Alteration to McMahon residence
        Original drawing: plan, interior and exterior elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. McMahon.
      - O.W. Miller residence., 1949.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 774. Addition to O.W. Miller residence
        13603 Hart Street, Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. O.W. Miller.
      - Plainer residence., 1949.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 793. Addition to Plainer residence
        7151 Woodley Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, elevations and detail.
        Owner: Mr. H.A. Plainer.
      - Jackson accessory building., 1949.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 795. Jackson accessory building
        12202 Addison Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. C. Jackson.
      - E. Miller residence., 1949.; 6.; 1 item.
        Job Number 798. Addition to E. Miller residence
        4125 Fulton Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E. Miller.
    - ., 1950 (Folder 190)
      - Rich residence., 1950.; 1.; 2 items.
        Addition to Rich residence
        5936 Woodlake Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, interior and exterior elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Frank Rich.
      - Kirsch residence., 1950-1954.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 820. Addition to Kirsch residence
        4816 Haskell Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. Kirsch.
      - Rockwell garage apartments., 1950.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 823. Rockwell garage apartments
        4437 Coldwater Canyon, North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. A.H. Rockwell.
    - (1 of 2)., 1951 (Folder 191)
      - Hardy accessory building., 1951.; 1.; 1 item.
        Hardy accessory building
        17142 Otsego St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Glenn Hardy.
      - Lowe garage., 1951.; 2.; 1 item.
        Lowe garage
      - Green residence., 1951, 1956.; 3.; 9 items.
        Job Number 866, 56-2. Additions to Green residence
        1100 Real Rd. Bakersfield, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. Green.
      - Webb residence., 1951.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 867. Additions to Webb residence
        4700 Noeline Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W. Webb.
      - Walker garage apartment., 1951.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 879. Walker garage apartment
        11932, 34 Burbank Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: C.W. Walker.
    - (2 of 2)., 1951 (Folder 192)
      - Horwath residence., 1951.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 892. Addition to Horwath residence
        12717 Bloomfield, North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: R.L. Horwath.
      - Holden residence., 1951.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 894. Addition to Holden residence
        7518 Hesperia Ave. Reseda, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section ,interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. and Mrs. C. Holden.
      - Buhler residence., 1951.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 912. Addition to Buhler residence
        5416 Woodman Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: John P. Buhler.
      - Gilmore residence., 1951.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 913. Addition to Gilmore residence
        14115 Green Leaf, Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, interior and exterior elevations and detail.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. A.W. Gilmore.
      - Yarnell residence., 1951.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 918. Revision of Yarnell residence
        Original drawings: plan and section.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Yarnell.
    - ., 1952 (Folder 193)
      - Christl residence., 1952.; 1.; 1 item.
        Addition to Christl residence
        4710 Noeline Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R.C. Christl.
      - Salvail residence., 1952.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 945, 974. Additions to Salvail residence, loggia & 3 car-port
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Salvail.
      - Woodward residence., 1952.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 961, 961-B. Addition & alteration to Woodward residence
        14226 Greenleaf Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, elevations and detail.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. G.K. Woodward.
      - Minter residence., 1952.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 966. Remodel of Minter residence
        18328 Plumer St. Northridge, CA.
        Original drawings: plans and section.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Gordon Minter.
      - Creed residence., 1952.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 982. Alteration to Creed residence
        4503 Atoll Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jimmy Creed.
      - Cramer residence., 1952.; 6.; 3 items.
        Job Number 984. Addition to Cramer residence
        22960 Erwin St. Woodland Hills, CA.
      - Cottrell residence., 1952.; 7.; 2 items.
        Job Number 987. Addition to Cottrell residence
        5446 Fulton Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Lester A. Cottrell.
    - ., 1953 (Folder 194)
      - Haney residence., 1953.; 1.; 1 item.
        Foundation for relocating Haney residence
        8200 Coldwater Canyon, North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Robert J. Haney.
      - Bower residence., 1953.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 53-15. Addition to Bower residence
        12035 Tiara St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dick Bower.
      - Beswick residence., 1953.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 53-23. Addition to Beswick residence
        702 South Brand, San Fernando, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Beswick.
      - Burroughs residence., 1953.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 53-24. Addition to Burroughs residence
        5001 Topeka, Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John Burroughs.
      - Lanai for Howland residence., 1953.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 53-39. Lanai for Howland residence
        5150 Amestoy Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Howland.
      - Session residence., 1953.; 6.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-40. remodeling of Session residence
        Adina Dr. Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Marc H. Session.
      - Salvail relocation and remodeling., 1953.; 7.; 2 items.
        Job Number 53-42. Salvail relocation and remodeling
        17710 Parthenia, Northridge, CA.
        Original drawings: plans and elevations. Engineer's calculations.
    - ., 1954 (Folder 195)
      - Warner residence., 1954.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 54-3. Patio Roof for Warner residence
        3860 Cochran Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. D.A. Warner.
      - Rothmund residence., 1954.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 54-21. Addition to Rothmund residence
        20120 Northridge Rd.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. C.R. Rothmund.
      - Morrison residence., 1954.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 54-26. Addition to Morrison residence
        4317 Elmer St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Max Morrison.
      - Emmons residence., 1954.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 54-48. Addition to Emmons residence
        Tujunga, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. D.W. Emmons.
    - (1 of 2)., 1955 (Folder 196)
      - Adams residence., 1955.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 55-2. Addition to Adams residence
        5020 Ledge Ave. Burbank, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Glenn Adams.
      - Bernheimer residence., 1955, 1960.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 55-14, 60-26. Additions to Bernheimer residence
        13255 Mulholland Dr. Beverly Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E.J. Bernheimer.
      - Kirsch pool pavilion & bath house., 1955.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-22. Kirsch pool pavilion & bath house
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John Kirsch.
      - Pecaro residence., 1955.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-29. Addition to Pecaro residence
        1060 Linda Flora Dr. West Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawing: plans and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. G. Pecaro.
      - Leiter residence., 1955.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-36. Remodeling of Leiter residence
    - (2 of 2)., 1955 (Folder 197)
      - Evans residence., 1955.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 55-53. Addition to Evans residence
        12752 Hortense.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Wm. Evans.
      - Morin residence., 1955.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-63. Addition to Morin residence
        7044 Calhoun Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawings: plan, section, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. P.T. Morin.
      - Harding residence., 1955.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-69. Addition to Harding residence
        11166 Valley Spring Ln. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, sections and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harding.
      - Ghormley residence., 1955.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 55-74. Addition to Ghormley residence
        1022 Ridgedale Ave. Beverly Hills, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. A.M. Ghormley.
      - Gross accessory building., 1955.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-76. Gross accessory building
        16523 Hartsook St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Gross.
    - ., 1956 (Folder 198)
      - Owens accessory pump house., 1956.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-12. Owens accessory pump house
        12815 Ventura Blvd. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. B.B. Owens.
      - Pritzlaff residence., 1956.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-14. Addition to Pritzlaff residence
        16820 Aldon Rd. Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, elevation, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Kipp Pritzlaff.
      - Foreman residence., 1956.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-16. Addition to Foreman residence
        17340 Rayen St. Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, elevation, details, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Chas. Foreman.
      - Fralic residence., 1956.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-23. Addition to Fralic residence
        7431 Gloria St. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, details, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Fralic.
      - Beaumont residence., 1956.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-33. Remodeling of Beaumont residence
        5426 Beckford, Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Al Beaumont.
      - Ciampa residence., 1956.; 6.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-48. Rumpus room for Ciampa residence
        1877 Hillside, Glendale, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Ciampa.
      - Stone residence., 1956.; 7.; 8 items.
        Job Number 56-49, 56-42, 57-57. Addition to Stone residence
        Rolling Stone ranch, New Hall, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, details, interior and exterior elevations and for residence and stables.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Cliff Stone.
      - Reynolds residence., 1956.; 8.; 2 items.
        Job Number 56-51. Remodeling and addition to Reynolds residence
        4302 Beeman, North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, details, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. Reynolds.
      - Eaton residence., 1956.; 9.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-52. Alterations and additions to Eaton residence
        4653 White Oak Pl. Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plan and elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Chas. Eaton.
    - ., 1957 (Folder 199)
      - Brace residence., 1957.; 1.; 1 item.
        Addition to Brace residence
        18050 Rancho Dr. Encino, CA. Original drawing: plan, section and elevations. Owner: Mr. James Brace.
      - Smith residence., 1957.; 2.; 1 item.
        Revision of Smith residence
        Original drawing: plan, section and elevation. Owner: Lonis D. Smith.
      - Lefevre residence., 1957.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 57-18. Addition to Lefevre residence
        Rancho Dr. Encino, CA. Original drawing: plan, section, details, interior and exterior elevations. Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. B. Lefevre.
      - Hampton residence., 1957.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 57-56. Addition to Hampton residence
        3870 Avenida del Sol, Studio City, CA. Original drawings: plans, sections and elevations. Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Orville Hampton.
    - ., 1958 (Folder 200)
      - Colm residence., 1958.; 1.; 11 items.
        Job Number 58-16, 954-A. Addition to Colm residence
        2930 22nd Street, Bakersfield, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W. F. Colm.
      - Williams residence., 1958.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 58-33. Remodeling and additions to Williams residence
        4200 Havenhurst Dr. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John T. Williams.
      - Knox residence., 1958.; 3.; 5 items.
        Job Number 58-34. Remodeling of Knox residence
        6133 S. Bonsal Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
      - O'Halloran car port., 1958.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 58-41. O'Halloran car port
        17931 Rancho Dr. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plan, elevation and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John F. O'Halloran.
      - Markoff residence., 1958.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 58-45. Remodeling of Markoff residence
        3363 Tareco Dr. Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations
        Owner: Morris K. Markoff.
      - Billingsley residence., 1958.; 6.; 4 items.
        Job Number 58-46. Addition to Billingsley residence
        Original drawing: plan, detail and interior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Glen Billingsley.
      - Cooley residence., 1958.; 7.; 6 items.
        Job Number 58-48. Addition to Cooley residence
        11047 De Soto, Chatsworth, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Robert J. Cooley.
    - ., 1959 (Folder 201)
      - Kristiansen residence., 1959.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 59-7. Remodeling of Kristiansen residence
        12148 Morrison St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plan, sections and elevation.
        Owner: Dr. Clarence Kristiansen.
      - Gross residence., 1959.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 59-9. Addition to Gross residence
        4647 Brewster Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Original drawings: plan, sections, elevations and details.
      - Brunner residence., 1959.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 59-20. Addition to Brunner residence
        19202 Santa Rita St. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Robert Brunner.
    - ., 1960 (Folder 202)
      - Mazzie residence., 1960.; 1.; 1 item.
        Additions & alterations to Mazzie residence
        1427 Camino Primavero, Bakersfield, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. Mazzie.
      - Johnson residence., 1960.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 60-8. Remodeling and additions to Johnson residence
        4653 Bellaire Ave. S.C. CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, elevation and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Ken Johnson.
      - Hanrahan residence., 1960.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-10. Remodeling and additions to Hanrahan residence
        10976 Art St. Sun Valley, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, sections and elevation.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Y. F. Hanrahan.
      - Sliva residence., 1960.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-12. Additions & alterations to Sliva residence
        5732 Donna Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Nick Sliva.
      - Hamlin residence., 1960.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-22. Addition for Hamlin residence
        Original drawing: plans, sections, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Hamlin.
      - Scott residence., 1960.; 6.; 4 items.
        Job Number 60-25. Addition for Scott residence
        4039 Havenhurst, Encino, CA.
        Copy of drawings: plans, section and elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jackson E. Scott.
      - Garabedian residence., 1960.; 7.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-32. Remodeling of Garabedian residence
        3863 Fredonia.
        Original drawing: plan, section, elevation and detail.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Garabedian.
      - Smith residence., 1960.; 8.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-37. Remodeling of Smith residence
        4929 Havenhurst, Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, section and elevation.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harley Smith.
      - Roth residence., 1960.; 9.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-38. Remodeling of Roth residence
        3769 Laurel Canyon, Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Morris Roth.
      - Bonaventura residence., 1960.; 10.; 1 item.
        Job Number 60-34. Remodeling of Bonaventura residence
        P.O. Box 11, Edison, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. James Bonaventura.
    - (1 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 203)
      - Kinney residence., 1961.; 1.; 1 item.
        Addition to Kinney residence
        17930 Rancho St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. P. B. Kinney.
      - Sykes residence., 1961.; 2.; 1 item.
        Addition to Sykes residence
        13759 Valley Vista, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H. S. Sykes.
      - Fisher residence., 1961.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 61-3. Revisions and additions to Fisher residence
        2387 Kimridge Rd. Beverly Hills, CA.
        Owner: R. E. Fisher.
      - Pomeroy residence., 1961.; 4.; 6 items.
        Job Number 61-12. Addition to Pomeroy residence
        4724 Louise Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Edna Pomery.
      - Gore residence., 1961.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-17. Addition to Gore residence
        216 N. Glenroy Ave. West LA, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section and elevation.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Gore.
      - Steinberg residence., 1961.; 6.; 2 items.
        Job Number 61-21. Remodeling of Steinberg residence
        4504 Petit Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, elevations and perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. M. Steinberg.
      - Voltz residence., 1961.; 7.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-28. Addition to Voltz residence
        5266 White Oak Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, elevation and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Voltz.
    - (2 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 204)
      - R. Nelson residence., 1961.; 1.; 2 items.